안녕하세요 여러분 오늘은 오늘의 영상은
제주도에서
가장 유명한
한화의
한화의 한화의
한화의 한화의 한화의 잘 안나가?
구석에 놓지마!
그리고 우선을 고치기 위한 손을 잡기 위해
소스와 물을 넣는다
이제 굽기!
아예 안 굽성..
이제 깨끗하게 굽는다 더욱 더 굳어진다
습관성 부하 굽는다
아직도 너무 신경쓰임 아직도 굽는다 아, 그럼 너무 싫다
오빤, 고기.
고기를 너른 자국으로
안녕하세요 여러분!
그리고, 대체로 행복하세요!
올해는 이렇게 끝이 났어요 아주 큰 성공이었어요 오늘 혼자서 오늘의 데이트를 하고 싶었는데
UPS 운전자가 1만장의 박스를 가져올 때까지 기다리고 있어요 왜냐면 제가 뉴욕에서 파파에 가져온 모든 것들은
캘리포니아로 돌아가서 그 배송이 안 오는 동안은 제가 집을 떠나서 그래서 오늘 모든 계획을 다 끊을 거예요
그래서 제가 집에서 조금 하루가 되어야 할 것 같아요 제가 생각하는 건...
아, 죄송해요 크리스마스 생일을 위에 두고
바닥에 편안하게 두고 제가 여기가 무슨 일이 있는지 보여주지 않았는데 근데 제가...
제가 자세히 보여주지 않았어요 눈에 좀 빛이 나고 싶어요
보이시나요?
완벽해 다시 해봤어요 마이크가 다시 안 연결이 됐어요 제 오디오가 다 빠졌어요 그래서 제가 조금씩 보셔서 보셔서
기다리세요
제가 너무 긴 일상에서
긴 일상에서 획득하고 있어요 모든 기회를 가지고 있는 것에 너무 고마워요 그리고 모든 도움이 되었을 때까지 매우 즐거운 일이었어요
하지만 저는 많은 것들을 뒷바람에 넣는 습관을 가지고 있는 습관을 알게 되었습니다 제 정신을 바꾸는 습관 시간이 부족하면
제가 말할게요 이달에 이것을 챙겨줄게요 이달에 이것을 챙겨줄게요 그리고 시간이 지나면 저는 완전히
지쳐졌어요 그래서 여기 제가 있습니다 스우시롤 밥상에 나가면서 K-드라마를 보고 있어요
이곳은 제 행복한 곳이에요 그리고 블러리 소스맨과 다시 한국에 택배가 왔어요
그는 아주 미친 시절이었고 매우忙했기 때문에 새해의 여행을 하고 싶었어요 블러리
소스맨의 하나의 장점이 그는 다른 사람들과 가족에 대해 너무 관심을 가지고 있어요 그리고 저는 그가 가장 아름다운 특징을 생각합니다.
가족도 저에게 매우 중요합니다.
그리고 저는 그 부분에 비슷한 가치를 공유하고 싶습니다.
우리는 정말 열심히 일하고 싶고, 우리의 부모님의 자유로운 일을 다시 한 조각을 더 받을 수 있도록 노력하고 싶습니다.
우리는 모두가 열심히 일하고, 또한, 흥미로운 기억을 만들기 위해 시간을 보내고, 함께 여행을 가질 수 있도록
노력하고 싶습니다.
시간은 계속 지나갑니다.
Really hard to find the right balance of working hard but also taking the time to build exciting memories and
Traveling together when we can.
Time feels like it's going by so fast and I get nervous sometimes because when I look back at the
Past few years everything just feels like a blur and my goal is to really soak in every moment not
Sprinting through the months and the year but taking it slow one day at a time so cheers to us
For making it to the end of the year If she's worried then we should take her out
And give her a massage But...
We can't...
We can't find a place to stay But...
I'm not a military doctor, you're the one who said that It is a human right It's true that I'm
Not a very good doctor
But only two people I'm sure that I'm the one who loves you the most.
Can you do this for me?
I'm sorry to say this while you're going through a hard time.
I have something to tell you.
It's no use telling you.
It's obvious if you hear it.
I haven't called my grandmother.
What phone number?
I created a collection with them.
They're such amazing partners.
So Helzberg Diamonds teamed out with Orate New York and together they created a new beautiful collection called Lore by
Orate, exclusive at Helzberg Diamonds.
And just like how you know Orate, everything is made with high quality.
It's ethically sourced.
But now you can see the pieces in person at the Helzberg store or of course online.
So I'm wearing some of my picks from their collection.
So first off, I'm wearing the diamond and bar hoop earrings.
These are so beautiful.
I just love wearing hoops on its own but you can always wear them stacked for my necklace it's a
Diamond baguette bar necklace and it's such a great layering piece I'm wearing it on its own and I think
It's really chic this is a vermeil paper clip and diamond bezel bracelet which is a great layering piece this
Is the diamond connection necklace which is one of my personal favorites mainly because the meaning is so beautiful it's
Two connected circles that represent the strongest connection in your life and it's made in this two-tone white and yellow
14 karat gold with a touch of diamond sparkle next this is the diamond x stud earrings I love stud
Earrings I think they're very easy I think these are fun and bold to wear on its own but simple
Enough to just have it for everyday wear and now that we're officially in holiday season I think all these
Pieces would make such beautiful and timeless gifts whether that is for yourself or a special someone you can use
My code mchoi 15 for 15 off lore by ore no minimum spend if you are stuck on some holiday
Gift ideas hope Hope you found this useful!
Oh, this is cute!
I look smart!
Oh these are so cute
Oh these are so cute wait, do I touch you?
No let's see
Good morning everyone, happy sunday I booked myself a pilates class
And I'm really regretting it but this is why I purposely booked my class last night last night so that
I'm forced to go and I can't change my mind.
I'm wearing my Jodi top from Little Puffy and this actually comes with the little like
Under layer bra.
It looks like this on the inside.
Off we go!
Off we go
Michelle?
I'm sorry I'll be back now in 10
Hello everyone my room right now it's empty I moved out my bed because I used this room as like
A temporary storage for all my pop-up boxes but everything is getting sent back to california so I just gotta
Get my life back together I was feeling very chatty so I wanted to do like an old school youtube
Style sit down talk about favorite products and I left it at the end in case for people who aren't
Interested to just like skip if you want starting off with makeup the most important part of my makeup is
Skin.
The foundation that I always always reach for every single day is the Clio cushion foundation.
I think these are better than a lot of like high-end cushion foundation.
Coverage is so beautiful.
Like I have it on right now and I just love how glowy and dewy my skin looks.
And this is like a mini mini version too.
It's so cute.
There's a pink in a black version and I love both.
And then on the topic of glowy skin, I am not a huge fan of very shimmery highlighters.
So the highlight that I have been loving this year is the Chanel Multibomb and this is in the Lilas
Color.
I love using this on my face.
Like I just kind of go over like high points of my cheeks.
It just gives me like the most natural glow and it looks like my My skin is just naturally so
Glowy.
If I'm wearing like an exposed shoulder like this.
So nice, right?
I am a big blush gal.
This is what I've been reaching a lot, like literally every single day.
This is the Chanel 798.
The very beautiful like rosy color.
And then on top of that I like to go in with the clio
Number five berry scoop blush which is like this pink color and I learned this from like korean makeup artists
On my look at youtube video she basically goes over the blush with like a pale pink color and it
Just gives like a very very natural, blended, airbrushed look
I would say this eyeliner, I have very oily lids this brand is actually really good, a lot of makeup
Artists use this as well I feel like it's hard to find in the states, I had to ask my
Friend to buy it for me in Korea.
The brand Pro8 Cheongdam and this is the gel liner.
The pencil liner.
When you go to Korea, I would highly recommend checking out this brand.
Next, I'm going to talk about perfumes.
I have three that I want to share today and this is like my favorite winter scents but also like
You can wear this any season.
First off is Byredo Mixed Emotions.
I think this is such a like badass.
I feel really cool when I spray this.
It's a very unique scent.
It all has like a smokiness to it.
Gypsy Water is a cult favorite.
Everyone loves this.
It smells so beautiful.
It's addicting.
I could smell this all day long.
This might not be like quote-unquote like a winter scent this is the dior blooming bouquet oh it just smells
So feminine so beautiful like I could wear this all year round but the reason why I would wear this
In the winter is because every time I spray this I get reminded of my korea trip with my mom
Because that's when I bought this and that's what I love about perfume like you spray it and it just
Brings you back to that particular memory and I think that's just so beautiful and
Next off this is the mighty patch nose from hero for anyone who has big nose pores like
Me I would say give this a try it's like it's like a pimple patch but it's for your nose
And it just soaks up all the oils from your pores my nose always feels like so smooth after and
Then for our armpits as As you guys know, this past year I have struggled with armpits and armpit
Sweat and BO.
I have PCOS so I get hormonal imbalance which causes my armpits to just react.
And one thing that really solved the problem is this deodorant.
Start and dry.
Looks like this.
Boom.
No more sweat.
Just like my armpits, I have dealt with dry scalp for so many years.
I have spent so much money in college getting scalp treatments.
I found the cure to my dry flaky scalp and it's Nizoral I can't believe I have waited this long
To discover this because my flaky scalp has been one of my biggest insecurities sorry but I'm gonna have to
Promote my own product but this is like my baby we did so many versions sampling with this boat it
Just looks so cute and hairstyle clip it boom
So cute
And for tech, I would say my LG Standby Me I'm not gonna bring it out, just put up a
Photo it's aesthetic, it's so functional like you can just wheel it around your house and use it watch tv
While you're cooking or in bed so I think that was one of the products that I used very well
This year next up is for my content creators I love tripods this is the fun one
I forget how long this stretches out.
I'll have it on the screen, but if you're wondering how I get those like weird angles that are filmed
From like so high up, it's this tripod.
That's it for now and I have so many other more favorites if you guys are interested.
Please let me know because I miss this type of filming and just talking about my favorite products so that's
It for now.
Happy December everyone!
You